infinixmobility.com 2018-01-12

# Infinix: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how Infinix, including its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Infinix,” “we,” “us,” “our”) collect, process, use, share, disclose, store, retain, and protect your information. It is significant that you read and understand the Privacy Policy since you use our services, you will be deemed to have accepted the practices mentioned in the Privacy Policy. If you are not satisfied with the practices described in the Privacy Policy, you should not use our Services. 

### **I.   Collection of Information**

####  **1.   Personal Information You Provided Directly**

When you make use of our products and services available on or through the official website located at  [infinixmobility.com](http://infinixmobility.com/) (the “Site”) or when you register an account with us, you may provide certain personally identifiable information about you that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or to identify an individual, including but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, user ID, password, phone number, fax number, contact preferences, date of birth, location, photos, videos and demographics (gender, age, occupation, company or organization name, language preference, city, country, zip code, area code, time zone, etc.). If you purchase services or products from us, we may also collect order number, transaction history, date/time of purchase, product information and error logs, refund history, credit and debit card information or other payment information, bank account information, the precise or approximate geo-location of your product, refund and repair information relating to your product, comments or feedback regarding the products or services, and other non-public information. We may store any information you provide us with information gathered from other sources, including the social accounts that you choose to associate with your use of the services, or with information we receive from other companies.

####  **2.   Non-Personal Information**

We may also collect certain non-personal information, which includes, without limitation, hardware model, device identifiers (e.g., IMEI, MEID, serial number, CID, MID and MCC ID Number or SIM card ID), MAC address, the date you activate your device, types and versions of your operating system, content you view or use and time-stamped logs of data exchanges, Internet Protocol (IP) address, usage statistics, performance statistics, browsing and navigational history, general geographic location, access times, browser type, the website that you visited prior to and after visiting the Site, the domain name of your Internet service provider, the applications and software that you download and install, your cellular carrier, your interaction with content and apps through our products or services. We may gather information about you from publicly and commercially available sources (as permitted by law), information about you from third-party social networking services when you choose to connect with those services or when we use third-party ad service providers to serve ads in our services. To deliver these ads, third parties automatically collect certain information about you and your devices and your use of the Site, including but not limited to the information mentioned above. 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, you hereby agree that such third parties as mentioned above may share your information as collected above with Infinix, which shall not be deemed as a breach of the confidentiality agreement, if any, between you and the third parties. In addition, by collecting your information from the third parties in the manner as mentioned above, Infinix shall not be deemed as accepting to be bound by any confidentiality agreement between you and the third parties regarding your information.

###  **II.   Processing and Use of Information**

We may process or use your information to arrange and process your orders, including confirmations, invoices, security alerts and support messages; to send you notices regarding your transactions, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies; to provide and deliver products and services that you purchase; to register, activate, validate and update your products or services; to respond to your inquiries and comments; to provide maintenance or to troubleshoot the Site, your products or services; to keep you posted on Infinix’s latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events; help us develop, operate, and improve our products, services, websites, marketing and customer communications; to investigate any fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity; to use for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis; to communicate with you about promotions and rewards about products and services offered by Infinix (you can unsubscribe from promotional emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link that is contained in each such email); to provide customized content and make recommendations based on your past activities on our services; to provide customized advertisements; to ask you for your opinions on our products and services and carrying out customer surveys.

###  **III.   Technologies**

We use different kinds of technologies to collect information when you use our services and products or visit the Site, which includes cookies, web beacons and other technologies, such as Local Shared Objects (LSOs, also called “Flash Cookies”). Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, mobile phone or other device. They can remember your data and settings, such as font size, and other preferences, which can help us to analyze your interaction with our website for the sake of promoting our services and your experience. Besides, they are beneficial for us to understand which portion of our website and which features are the most popular. We also use information gathered from cookies to target our advertising. Web beacons are electronic images embedded in online content, videos, and emails, and can allow a server to read certain types of information from your computer or mobile phone and count visits. We use cookies to store your preferences based on what you view on the Site in order to personalize your visit. 

When accessing the Site, you can change your browser settings to delete or prevent cookies from being stored on your computer or mobile phone by checking the“help” menu of your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Nevertheless, some services may be designed to work using cookies, and disabling cookies may affect your ability to use those services, or certain portion of them. 

By accessing and using our services, you consent to the storage of cookies, other local storage technologies, beacons and other information on your devices. You also consent to the access of such cookies, local storage technologies, beacons and information by us and by the third parties mentioned above. 

### **IV.   Disclosure to Third Parties**

We may share your personal information with our affiliates, business partners or corporations who provide services such as processing information, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. We may also share your information when required by law, legal process, litigation, and requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence to disclose your personal information. We may also reveal your information if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. In addition, in the course of a reorganization, merger, acquisition, or in the event of bankruptcy we may disclose any and all personal information provided to the relevant third party. We will not disclose your information to third parties for their own independent marketing or business purposes without your consent. 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, you hereby waive the right to raise claims against Infinix, including its subsidiaries and affiliates, for the above sharing, disclosing and revealing of your information. 

### **V.   Retention of Information**

We will safeguard all of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your personal information may be retained for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Policy, or for a period that is required or permitted by relevant laws and regulations.

###  **VI.   Location-Based Services**

When we provide location-based services on Infinix products, we may collect and use the real-time geo-location data, which can be obtained from Global Positioning System information (GPS), Wi-Fi hotspot, Bluetooth, or ID number of the signal tower of your carrier network. You can turn on, change, or turn off your GPS information by going into the GPS settings on the product, but you may not have the right to control Wi-Fi and ID numbers of the signal tower of your carrier network since this relies on your carrier’s policy.

###  **VII.   Protection of Personal Information**

We attempt to safeguard personal information by taking appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures against any unauthorized access or use of your personal information. Even though we will take reasonable steps to use and improve various safeguards, no system or technology is completely secure. However, please note that even though we will take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure. Besides, we are not responsible for the security of any independent third-party applications and services or the data those third-party applications and services may collect about you. Please ask those third parties how they keep your data safe.

Please note that the personal information you choose to share in some circumstances may be accessible to other users and can be read, collected, copied, republished or used by them. You shall be independently responsible for the personal information you choose to share or submit in such circumstances. You should be careful to decide what personal information you want to share or submit. 

### **VIII.   Protection of Minors **

We highly value the protection of personal information of minors. If you are a minor, you should ask your guardian to read and understand this Privacy Policy carefully. You should warrant that you use our services and/or provide us with information after you have obtained the prior consent of your guardian. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, minor herein shall have the meaning as defined by the laws in force in the country where the minor’s habitual residence locates.

###  **IX.   Changes to Privacy Policy**

This Policy may be amended from time to time. When we change the policy, there will or WILL NOT be a notice be posted on the Site and the new Policy will be effective immediately after it is posted on the Site. You should check this Policy for new updates on a regular basis. When required by law, any material changes in the manner that we collect, process, use, share, disclose, store, retain, and protect personally identifiable information will apply only to information collected after posting of the revised Policy. 

### **X.   Applicable Law and Dispute Resolution**

Any dispute, claim, difference or other controversy arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy shall be governed by, construed and interpreted in accordance with the law of Hong Kong, without giving effect to principles of conflicts of law therewith. Any dispute or difference regarding this Privacy Policy which cannot be settled amicably shall be referred to and finally resolved by arbitration administered by the Hong Kong International Arbitration Centre (HKIAC) under the Hong Kong International Arbitration Centre Administered Arbitration Rules in force when the Notice of Arbitration is submitted. The seat of arbitration shall be Hong Kong. The arbitration language will be English. The award of arbitration shall be final and binding the disputing parties.

###  **XI.   Questions and Contact**

If you have any questions or concerns relating to our Privacy Policy or if you would like to make complaints about violation of local privacy laws, you can always contact us at (hello@infinixmobility.com). 

Copyright © 2017 Infinix Inc. All rights reserved.
